There is an issue of will.
Come out!
In the name of Jesus Christ!
Deliverance in Jesus' Name
Come here!
There is an issue of will.
God loves you.
That is why they have attempted to separate you from your loved ones.
Pray against the spirit of death that keeps appearing to you.
Your dear ones who are dead keep appearing to you when you sleep.
They keep talking with you and do everything with you.
By the time you wake up, you realise that they are dead.
"Why am I seeing dead people?"
You are correct, sir.
Come out in the name of Jesus!
Thank You, Lord.
Deliverance in Jesus' Name
TESTIMONY TIME
Good morning, Church.
My name is Helen Nathaniel.
I am a civil servant and I live in Abuja (Nigeria).
The problem that brought me to The SCOAN was the problem of seized menstruation,
for seventeen years.
During this period, I was always seeing dead people in my dreams.
I went to many hospitals when this problem started,
as far back as 1997.
I have been to many specialist hospitals.
The doctors were able to diagnose hormonal imbalance.
All the hospitals I went to in Abuja, Lagos, Ibadan, diagnosed hormonal imbalance.
At a stage, I got tired of taking the pills they were always administering to me.
Because at the end of the day, there was no solution, no results.
I am not talking of seventeen days, weeks, or months, but seventeen good years.
And as a woman, you know the implications.
I was doing that and at a stage, I had nothing more to sow.
I decided to pray on my own.
I started staying indoors on Sundays; I didn't go out.
One day I was just strolling out and somebody gave me a flyer
and asked me to come to a certain church.
I wondered if it wasn't like the other churches.
I just summoned up courage and went there.
On getting to that church, something happened.
The man of God there asked all the church members
to go and install Emmanuel TV in their homes.
I went out, bought my own and installed it.
The very day I installed it, Senior Prophet T.B. Joshua appeared to me in my dream.
He started deliverance right in this church.
After installing Emmanuel TV?
Yes, sir.
The very day I installed it, Senior Prophet T.B. Joshua appeared to me in my dream.
He started deliverance right in this church.
So I found myself in this auditorium.
He conducted deliverance on me and two dwarfs left my body.
Dwarfs?
Yes, two left my body in that dream and the church started clapping.
The dwarfs were wearing bedroom slippers.
They were just jumping about.
I was born in Lagos and I grew up in Lagos.
I received both my basic and tertiary education here in the Southwest
but I have never been to The SCOAN.
After I had prayed with the man of God on Emmanuel TV, I slept again.
This was the second time.
This time, I saw the man of God in my village
and he prayed with me in that dream.
After that prayer, I said, "Ok, maybe it's time to visit The SCOAN".
So, I made up my mind and came.
But something happened on the day I came here. That was on the 11th of January 2015.
When I was at the entrance,
the ushers gave me a pass but I said, "No, I will not take it".
They said, "Madam, take your pass. Go in!" but I said, "No, I will not enter the church!"
"Take it!" and I said, "No!"
The ushers were very very patient with me.
They were able to calm the spirit
because I know it was the spirit that was at work.
I now came in. When I came in, I got a place and sat down.
Why did you refuse to come in?
I don't know. I came all the way from Abuja.
Can you imagine that? Somebody who came to The SCOAN
and at the entrance with the opportunity to enter, she said she's not entering again.
Can you see the reason why dwarfs came out?
Testimony Time
Ms Helen Nathaniel - Prophecy Testimony
When the man of God came out and started giving prophecies,
that was how he was able to locate me
as can be seen in the clip we watched.
Before I came here, I was seeing dead people.
All the prophecies the man of God gave to me were all accurate.
I was arranged for prayer line.
Along the prayer line, the man of God prayed for us.
The first time he passed, he touched my head.
The second time he passed, he touched my tummy.
When I got to where I was staying, in the night, between 1am and 2am, something happened.
My lower region - from my lower abdomen down - started shaking; it started vibrating.
Then, I felt something like a rod inside me with force
as if somebody used an iron to push inside my body.
I jumped out of the bed.
My legs started shaking. The left leg became paralyzed
and there was a mark that I saw there.
I was afraid, I didn't know it was deliverance that was taking place.
I was so scared.
When I saw the mark on my legs, I could not even stand.
In the morning, I discovered that the menses that seized for seventeen years had started flowing.
Ms Helen Nathaniel - Prophecy Testimony
God used the prophecy of the man of God to restore my menses.
For the past one year and three months, I don't have any problem with my menses.
It has been flowing normally.
I give God all the glory.
Ms Helen Nathaniel - Prophecy Testimony
My advice to the viewers all over the world is to just be patient and trust in God.
It is only God that can do it.
I advise them to look for a living church and be worshipping there.